<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<sites>
	<site>
		<locationName>England</locationName>
		<xPosition>400</xPosition>
		<yPosition>100</yPosition>
		<sourceDir>Adam</sourceDir>
		<profileImage>portrait.jpg</profileImage>
        <videoFile>avalanche.flv</videoFile>
		<people>
			<names>Adam</names>
			<story>
            Adam (Standard Hebrew: אָדָם, masculine proper noun; Arabic: آدم) was the first man created by God, according to Book of Genesis, and noted in subsequent Jewish, Christian and Islamic commentary. He is considered a prophet by the Islamic, Mormon, Mandaean and Bahá'í faiths.
            In Islam, Adam is considered the first Prophet of God and the husband of Eve (Arabic: Hawwa) who was created from Adam by the "will of God". Satan had lured Adam and Eve into disobeying God by tasting from the forbidden tree (although no reference is necessary as to what he may have tasted). This was the first act of revenge from Satan for being banished from the kingdom of heaven due to mankind. An important point to note here is that the Qur'an does not state or imply that it was Eve who tempted Adam to disobey God.
            In the Bahá'í view, Adam was the first Manifestation of God in recorded history. He is believed by Bahá'ís to have started the Adamic cycle 6000 years ago, which has culminated with Bahá'u'lláh. The Biblical story of Adam and Eve, according to Bahá'í belief, is allegorical and is explained by `Abdu'l-Bahá in Some Answered Questions; in the Bahá'í view, in the biblical story Eve represents Adam's soul and the serpent represents attachment to the material world, and that ever since his fall, the human race has been conscious of good and evil.
            </story>
		</people>
	</site>
	<site>
		<locationName>Japan</locationName>
		<xPosition>50</xPosition>
		<yPosition>50</yPosition>
		<sourceDir>Jim</sourceDir>
		<profileImage>jim_portrait.jpg</profileImage>
        <videoFile>jims_movie.flv</videoFile>
		<people>
			<names>Jim</names>
			<story>
            James Laing, son of John and Margaret Bowie Laing, was born at Slamanan, near  the city of Glasgow, Scotland, January 2, 1846.
            Mr. Laing's parents, realizing the larger possibilities that the United  States offered, emigrated with their family to America in 1866, settling in Mercer county, Pennsylvania, where they engaged in farming and mining. On December 31, 1872, Mr. Laing was married to Susanna Kay, second daughter  of Thomas and Janet Kerr Kay. Miss Kay was a Scotch lady, born at Lanark, Scotland, April 29, 1851, and came to America with her parents in 1870. The Kay family settled first in Sharon, Pa., and later in West Virginia.
            Mr. Laing bought a large tract of coal land in West Virginia and moved with his family of two children to Quinnimont, Fayette county, in 1878. At this time the New River coal fields were just beginning to be developed. Mr. Laing organized the Royal Coal and Coke Company in 1891 and opened up the Royal mine, which was the first mine to be operated in Raleigh county, and was managed by Mr. Laing until 1896, when he organized the Sun Coal and Coke Company and sank the first shaft ever used in the New River coal field, at Sun, which he managed with remarkable effectiveness and success. Mr. Laing continued the management of these mines until 1904, when he retired from active service in mining operations, though he continued his interest in other activities, and until the time of his death was president of the Laing Mining Company, the McKinley Land Company, the Craig-Giles Iron Company and the Mountain Lake Land Company.
            Mr. Laing had long dreamed of spending his declining years in a quiet country community, and selecting the small but well-known town of Lewisburg, purchased property and built a large and handsome stone house, "Canipsie Glen," into which he moved his family from Fayette county, in 1904.Mr. Laing was a trustee of the Lewisburg Seminary, from which institution his daughters received their education. This school was dear to his heart and he labored zealously for its development and power. His interest in Christian education was felt over the entire church, and in 1907, shortly before his death, he was appointed a trustee of Hampden-Sidney College, where two of his sons had been educated.
            He was just realizing the ambition of his boyhood comfort and quietness for himself and his loyal and saintly wife and having a constructive part in the education of the youth of his beloved State and church-when his death occurred, after a brief illness, at his home in Lewisburg, October 31, 1907. Surviving him are his widow and seven children: Janet Kerr, John Bowie, Thomas Kay, Annie Jean, James Kay, Susanna Kay (Mrs. R. L. Speas), and Bessie Belle.
            Like most of his Scotch countrymen, Mr. Laing was an ardent Presbyterian, devoted to his church and liberal in its support. While at Quinnimont, in 1882, he was ordained a ruling elder in the church, and with a fidelity and fitness realized by few, he served in that sacred capacity wherever he lived.
            Mr. Laing lived in Lewisburg only three short years, but it was long enough to win an enviable place in the esteem and friendship of the people of the town and community. In politics, he was a Republican, believing firmly in the McKinley principles of protection. As a man and citizen his life and conduct were ever above reproach, modest and unassuming, true to his convictions and firm in his stand for right as he saw it; he held the respect and confidence of those who knew him best and was admired and honored by his many business associates and employees. In his death his family lost one of the truest and best husbands and fathers, the schools of which he was a trustee a wise and trusted counsellor, his town and State a constructive and loyal citizen, and the church, his choicest pride, a most faithful member and officer.
            </story>
		</people>
	</site>
	<site>
		<locationName>Australia</locationName>
		<xPosition>800</xPosition>
		<yPosition>400</yPosition>
		<sourceDir>OHOLYJESUS</sourceDir>
		<profileImage>Barzoni-Black-Jesus-Montage-Vincent-Barzoni.jpeg</profileImage>
        <videoFile>jesus_the_musical.flv</videoFile>
		<people>
			<names>Jesus</names>
			<story>
            Jesus (7–2 BC/BCE to 26–36 AD/CE), also known as Jesus of Nazareth (or Jesus the Nazarene), was a 1st century Jewish teacher who is the central figure of Christianity, and is also an important figure in several other religions. He is also called Jesus Christ, where "Christ" is a title derived from the Greek Χριστός (Christós), meaning the "Anointed One," which corresponds to the Hebrew-derived "Messiah". The name "Jesus" is an anglicization of the Greek Ίησους (Iēsous), itself a Hellenization of the Hebrew יהושע (Yehoshua) or Hebrew-Aramaic ישוע (Yeshua), meaning "YHWH rescues".
            The main sources of information regarding Jesus' life and teachings are the four canonical Gospels of the New Testament: Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John. Most scholars in the fields of history and biblical studies agree that Jesus was a Galilean Jew, was regarded as a teacher and healer, was baptized by John the Baptist, and was crucified in Jerusalem on orders of the Roman Governor Pontius Pilate on the charge of sedition against the Roman Empire. Few critical scholars believe that all ancient texts on Jesus' life are either completely accurate or completely inaccurate.
            Christian views of Jesus (see also Christology) center on the belief that Jesus is Divine and is the Messiah whose coming was promised in the Old Testament and that he was resurrected after his crucifixion. Christians predominantly believe that Jesus is God incarnate, who came to provide salvation and reconciliation with God. Other Christian beliefs include Jesus' virgin birth, performance of miracles, fulfillment of biblical prophecy, ascension into Heaven, and future Second Coming. Nontrinitarianism profess various other interpretations regarding his divinity (see below).
            In Islam, Jesus (Arabic: عيسى‎, commonly transliterated as Isa) is considered one of God's important prophets, a bringer of scripture, a worker of miracles, and the Messiah. Muslims, however believe Jesus was not divine and not crucified, but ascended bodily to heaven.
            </story>
		</people>
	</site>
</sites>